<source><jobs><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US / Remote</location><title>Machine Learning PhD Scientist</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>67668</job_reference><company>Ten Lives</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/e831961d555ac79ac4d50f463f10bdbd3cfc71ad.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/ten-lives</company_website><company_description>Decarbonizing food proteins with AI.</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/67668</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Ten Lives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ten Lives (YC S22) is pioneering research in AI and biology to feed the world, sustainably. Our flagship brand decarbonizes the pet food industry by reducing the fifth of the world’s meat consumed by pets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ten Lives is tackling the climate emergency by optimizing microbial factories with AI. With backing from YC / Collab Fund and NSF grants, we’re decoding the microbial genome to produce food proteins at the lowest cost and environmental impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ten Lives is seeking a motivated Machine Learning Scientist to tackle the problem of DNA sequence design. This position offers an opportunity to work at the forefront of AI research, applying advances from natural language processing to the language of life - DNA. As an early employee, you will have the opportunity to lead research initiatives and collaborate with our interdisciplinary team of computational and experimental scientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we offer at Ten Lives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Real impact. Ten Lives can directly reduce global emissions by 1% by 2040.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Supportive environment to explore, innovate, and drive research direction.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We encourage publishing and presenting scientific findings.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary, comprehensive health insurance, PTO, and 401(k) matching.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hybrid / remote-friendly.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implement, optimize, and deploy state-of-the-art machine learning models for DNA sequence design.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop efficient, robust code and data pipelines, ensuring high-quality results.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analyze and interpret computational approaches, presenting findings to colleagues in regular update meetings.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Establish automated processes to continually evaluate and enhance our design methodology.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with diverse teams across biology and machine learning, contributing to the scientific and strategic vision of the company.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;PhD degree in Machine Learning, Mathematics, Computational Biology, Statistics, Physics, or related disciplines.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to implement and analyze state-of-the-art models for sequential data (text / genomic / time series) and/or expertise in explainability methods.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in writing clean and efficient code and deploying services on cloud computing platforms like GCP, AWS, or Azure.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interest in climate solutions and likes cats.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$150K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$225K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>AI Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>67410</job_reference><company>Chima</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/a5536faf0c37956706227c0349f57943e972007e.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/chima</company_website><company_description>Building infrastructure tools to help large companies customize their LLMs.</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/67410</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Chima&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Chima, we're helping the world's most important institutions customize and scale their generative AI. Our technology lets our customers integrate and analyze their data and relevant public data sources so they can leverage commercial generative AI models privately, in a way that they couldn't before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chima is seeking highly skilled generative AI Engineers to join our team. As an AI Application Engineer, you will be responsible for designing, developing, and deploying cutting-edge AI models to solve enteprises' biggest problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What you’ll do:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Develop new user-facing features.&lt;/strong&gt; Build high-quality generative AI features and ship quickly.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experiment and improve our AI infrastructure.&lt;/strong&gt; You’ll lead our implementation of new AI features and cutting-edge frameworks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Earn trust with customers.&lt;/strong&gt; Talk with leaders from early-stage startups, growth-stage businesses, and large enterprises to understand their AI needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Build our team.&lt;/strong&gt; We’re growing, and you will work directly with the CEO, CTO, and other founding members to bring in talented AI engineers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Role and responsibilities:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design and develop advanced generative models that drive specific business applications.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take ownership of certain customers' generative AI deployment and spear head product work for them.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Conduct research and stay up-to-date with the latest advancements in generative AI, including techniques such as GANs, VAEs, and autoregressive models.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work closely with cross-functional teams to develop and implement generative AI models that can solve complex business problems and drive innovation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with our customers' senior executives, engineers, data scientists, product managers and machine learning experts to build end-to-end AI solutions that can be deployed at scale.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our Tech stack is extremely expansive and involves rapidly. Instead of being prescriptive in requirements here, we are looking for someone with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Publications in top AI conferences.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience at elite AI research labs (OpenAI, Google Brain, DeepMind).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience on world-class AI products (Search, Recommendation, Ads).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Open-source projects / contributions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Next Steps:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please fill out the following Google form to have us reach out to you with next steps:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://forms.gle/Bqq3vJ7RmJHgHUsE9"&gt;https://forms.gle/Bqq3vJ7RmJHgHUsE9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;Technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our Tech stack is extremely expansive and involves rapidly. Instead of being prescriptive here, we are looking for someone with:-Publications in top AI conferences.-Experience at AI research labs (OpenAI, Google Brain, DeepMind).-Experience on world-class AI products (Search, Recommendation, Ads).-Open-source projects / contributions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$100K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$300K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>AI Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>66955</job_reference><company>Artisan</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/8957949d15333742c1433b49acab5c0938b462cc.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/artisan</company_website><company_description>AI Employees Called Artisans, Starting With An AI BDR</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/66955</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Artisan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Artisan, we're on a mission to create the most advanced human-like digital workers, called Artisans, and the software operating system for startups across verticals. We're starting with sales through our Artisan Sales platform and Ava, The Sales Rep Artisan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our first Artisan, Ava, is a BDR who automates the entire outbound sales process and can be set up with a 10-minute conversation. Ava creates the user's ICP, prospects with her database of over 270M contacts, does lead research, crafts &amp;amp; sends highly bespoke email sequences, and books meetings into sales reps' calendars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We recently launched Artisan Labs, our research lab where we're pioneering the foundational technologies required to create human-like digital workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the next Industrial Revolution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artisan is seeking an AI Engineer to become part of our rapidly expanding team. We're creating the most advanced AI employees on the market and exceptional software products for them and human teams to use, starting with sales and rapidly expanding into other verticals. We were a part of the Y Combinator W24 batch, have raised over $7.4M in seed capital, and are relentlessly working to become the market leader in this space and build the future of work and software.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you pursue excellence in your work, thrive in fast-paced settings and are an extraordinarily talented backend engineer with a strong educational and career background, we would love to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fine-tuning and prompt engineering LLMs for our Artisans, helping us to create the most advanced AI Employees (primarily Google's Gemini, OpenAI's GPT 3.5, GPT 4 &amp;amp; GPT-4o, and Anthropic's Claude).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Developing systems to allow users to interact with platform features through chat (e.g. our onboarding flow and platform setup is currently done by Ava, The Sales Rep Artisan).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Architect LLM systems which integrate with third-party tools for a plethora of Artisan use cases (think email conversations, the user chat interface, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimize occurrences of hallucinations and strange tone of voice.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop new email Playbooks which execute research &amp;amp; writing workflows typically done by human sales reps.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reduce latency of our LLM systems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stay up-to-date with the latest LLM technologies so we stay on the bleeding edge of what's possible.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Degree in Computer Science, Machine Learning, Data Science, or a related field.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Industry experience with LLM fine tuning and prompt engineering.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in Python and MLOps tools like MLFlow and cloud platforms such as Azure or AWS.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Python back-end development.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Generous equity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Great health + vision + dental.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$90K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$150K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>New York, NY, US</location><title>Machine Learning Researcher</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>66366</job_reference><company>Output Biosciences</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/990074a168ed566a1898edae4ddc84a3de0b15c3.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/output</company_website><company_description>Teaching Generative AI the Language of Biology</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/66366</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Output Biosciences&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.outputbio.com/"&gt;Output Biosciences&lt;/a&gt; is pioneering Biologically-Aware Generative AI to finally understand complex biological systems. We are building Large Biological Models that can generate breakthrough medicines and transform the way we diagnose, treat and prevent disease. Output was founded by &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/adi-mashiach/"&gt;Adi Mashiach, MD&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/mirella-mashiach/"&gt;Mirella Mashiach&lt;/a&gt;. Adi is third time founder of AI-driven biotech startups (first was acquired, second is on Nasdaq), a former physician and researcher in computational systems biology focused on nonlinear dynamics; Mirella is a former big pharma exec and biotech investor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;Torch/PyTorch, Python, TensorFlow, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Amazon Web Services (AWS)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join us in creating biological reasoning in generative AI to revolutionize disease understanding and treatment. As a machine learning researcher, you'll work alongside our founders to build a biologically-aware AI platform that understands complex biological relationships and generates novel therapeutics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;⁠You will develop new approaches to infuse biological understanding into AI models, innovating on key architectural components to unlock unprecedented capabilities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will design and train innovative AI models using large, diverse biological datasets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will tackle unique challenges such as extremely long context in biological sequences and multi-modal data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will solve challenging AI research problems at scale, tackling key aspects such as model architecture and scaling, pre-training and fine-tuning strategies, and rigorous evaluation methods&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your work will span various Gen AI architectures, including transformers, autoencoders, GANs, and diffusion models, as well as additional deep learning architectures&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make a real tangible impact on millions of lives by pushing the boundaries of generative AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No prior biological background required&lt;/strong&gt;--we'll bring you up to speed on everything you need to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who We’re Looking For&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering, or a relevant technical field&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have a Master's degree with 3 years of industry experience or a PhD with 2 years of research or industry experience in Machine Learning, Applied Statistics, Computer Science, or other relevant fields&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have experience writing software and executing complex experiments using Python with machine learning frameworks such as TensorFlow, PyTorch, and Scikit-learn&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have researched and developed deep learning and generative AI methods&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have experience scaling machine learning models in a cloud computing environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You take pride in delivering high-quality, clean, efficient, and maintainable code, with a keen eye for appropriate design patterns and software architectures&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You exhibit a proactive approach to problem-solving, thinking beyond the specific task, taking ownership of challenges, and pride in solving them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have a mature mindset in ambiguous situations, helping to frame questions and seek clarity while making decisions in the face of uncertainty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are a clear and concise communicator, conveying information effectively in written and verbal communication, and enjoy collaborating with and guiding colleagues in a multidisciplinary team&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are motivated by making a real impact and are committed to tackling problems of significant consequence with determination and creativity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are a first author on a publication or peer-reviewed AI conference paper&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have previous experience applying machine learning in biology or chemistry&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have knowledge of physics, molecular biology, chemistry, or related fields&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have experience in developing efficient code in C/C++&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Values&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;❤️ &lt;strong&gt;Heart:&lt;/strong&gt; We foster a culture of ownership. We are assembling a team of individuals who are passionate and take pride in their contributions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;🏆 &lt;strong&gt;Excellence:&lt;/strong&gt; We have an unwavering commitment to excellence and continuously challenge ourselves to reach the highest standards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;🚀 &lt;strong&gt;Practicality:&lt;/strong&gt; We value practicality and results-oriented thinking. We are committed to making a tangible impact on the lives of our patients and the broader community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;📣 &lt;strong&gt;Honesty:&lt;/strong&gt; We place a high value on honesty and directness. We firmly believe in addressing issues as they arise, in an open and transparent manner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;🎮 &lt;strong&gt;Fun:&lt;/strong&gt; We believe that life is too short to not have fun. That's why we're committed to creating an engaging and enjoyable work environment. Our goal is to create a workplace that is fun, rewarding and fulfilling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We encourage new and different ideas, creativity and contrarian thinking. We are looking forward to further shaping our culture with early team members. You'll have a chance to make your mark!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You own your day-to-day management. We don't care when or where you work, we care if we all hit our milestones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary and equity in a growing, well-funded startup&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent medical, dental, and vision coverage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Healthy feedback focused environment to help you strive - leadership will have high expectations, regularly share constructive feedback, support you and help you grow, and welcome receiving feedback and ideas from you&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$110K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>New York, NY, US</location><title>Machine Learning Researcher (PhD)</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>66365</job_reference><company>Output Biosciences</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/990074a168ed566a1898edae4ddc84a3de0b15c3.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/output</company_website><company_description>Teaching Generative AI the Language of Biology</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/66365</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Output Biosciences&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.outputbio.com/"&gt;Output Biosciences&lt;/a&gt; is pioneering Biologically-Aware Generative AI to finally understand complex biological systems. We are building Large Biological Models that can generate breakthrough medicines and transform the way we diagnose, treat and prevent disease. Output was founded by &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/adi-mashiach/"&gt;Adi Mashiach, MD&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/mirella-mashiach/"&gt;Mirella Mashiach&lt;/a&gt;. Adi is third time founder of AI-driven biotech startups (first was acquired, second is on Nasdaq), a former physician and researcher in computational systems biology focused on nonlinear dynamics; Mirella is a former big pharma exec and biotech investor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;Torch/PyTorch, Python, TensorFlow, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Amazon Web Services (AWS)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join us in creating biological reasoning in generative AI to revolutionize disease understanding and treatment. As a machine learning researcher, you'll work alongside our founders to build a biologically-aware AI platform that understands complex biological relationships and generates novel therapeutics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;⁠You will develop new approaches to infuse biological understanding into AI models, innovating on key architectural components to unlock unprecedented capabilities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will design and train innovative AI models using large, diverse biological datasets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will tackle unique challenges such as extremely long context in biological sequences and multi-modal data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will solve challenging AI research problems at scale, tackling key aspects such as model architecture and scaling, pre-training and fine-tuning strategies, and rigorous evaluation methods&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your work will span various Gen AI architectures, including transformers, autoencoders, GANs, and diffusion models, as well as additional deep learning architectures&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make a real tangible impact on millions of lives by pushing the boundaries of generative AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No prior biological background required&lt;/strong&gt;--we'll bring you up to speed on everything you need to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who We’re Looking For&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering, or a relevant technical field&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have a PhD in Deep Learning, Artificial Intelligence or other relevant field with 2 years of research or industry experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have first author publications experience at peer-reviewed AI conferences or journals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have experience writing software and executing complex experiments using Python with machine learning frameworks such as TensorFlow, PyTorch, and Scikit-learn&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have researched and developed deep learning and generative AI methods&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have experience scaling machine learning models in a cloud computing environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You take pride in delivering high-quality, clean, efficient, and maintainable code, with a keen eye for appropriate design patterns and software architectures&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You exhibit a proactive approach to problem-solving, thinking beyond the specific task, taking ownership of challenges, and pride in solving them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have a mature mindset in ambiguous situations, helping to frame questions and seek clarity while making decisions in the face of uncertainty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are a clear and concise communicator, conveying information effectively in written and verbal communication, and enjoy collaborating with and guiding colleagues in a multidisciplinary team&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are motivated by making a real impact and are committed to tackling problems of significant consequence with determination and creativity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus Points&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have previous experience applying machine learning in biology or chemistry&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have knowledge of physics, molecular biology, chemistry, or related fields&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have experience in developing efficient code in C/C++&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our Values&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;❤️ &lt;strong&gt;Heart:&lt;/strong&gt; We foster a culture of ownership. We are assembling a team of individuals who are passionate and take pride in their contributions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;🏆 &lt;strong&gt;Excellence:&lt;/strong&gt; We have an unwavering commitment to excellence and continuously challenge ourselves to reach the highest standards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;🚀 &lt;strong&gt;Practicality:&lt;/strong&gt; We value practicality and results-oriented thinking. We are committed to making a tangible impact on the lives of our patients and the broader community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;📣 &lt;strong&gt;Honesty:&lt;/strong&gt; We place a high value on honesty and directness. We firmly believe in addressing issues as they arise, in an open and transparent manner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;🎮 &lt;strong&gt;Fun:&lt;/strong&gt; We believe that life is too short to not have fun. That's why we're committed to creating an engaging and enjoyable work environment. Our goal is to create a workplace that is fun, rewarding and fulfilling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We encourage new and different ideas, creativity and contrarian thinking. We are looking forward to further shaping our culture with early team members. You'll have a chance to make your mark!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You own your day-to-day management. We don't care when or where you work, we care if we all hit our milestones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary and equity in a growing, well-funded startup&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent medical, dental, and vision coverage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Healthy feedback focused environment to help you strive - leadership will have high expectations, regularly share constructive feedback, support you and help you grow, and welcome receiving feedback and ideas from you&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$110K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>Sales Engineer (New Grad)</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>65723</job_reference><company>Promoted.ai</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/bd28656a2bd5b2cc24a2d0577bedc594f2e0ffe7.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/promoted</company_website><company_description>Dramatically better search and ads for marketplaces</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/65723</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Promoted.ai&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Promoted dramatically improves search and discovery relevance and ads quality at scale, like at our customers Upwork, Eventbrite, and Outschool. We combine the best of traditional ML and streaming data infra with the latest in LLM AI to optimize the balance between relevance, revenue, and profitability. We're ex-Google, Meta, and Pinterest ads engineers, and we've built this before together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you join Promoted, you’ll get the benefits of:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;San Francisco Office - Our office space is open and available&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Healthcare Plans - We have options for you and your family&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FSA/HSA - You can opt into these savings plans&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dependant Care Account - For eligible care savings&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;401k - We offer it and match your first 6%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;PerkSpot Account - Trusted employee discounts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitive and transparent compensation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, mental or physical disability, gender identity or Veteran status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Promoted is an enterprise B2B SaaS AI startup in San Francisco. We solve search and ads relevance for companies where relevance is the critical driver of business success: large online marketplaces and scaled e-commerce companies. We combine the best of the last generation of ML with the latest in LLM technologies to increase revenue by 5-10% from dramatically better search, recommendations, and native ads. We are hiring a Sales Engineer to join our dynamic team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Role Overview&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a Sales Engineer at &lt;a href="http://Promoted.ai"&gt;Promoted.ai&lt;/a&gt;, you will bridge the gap between our AI technology and our clients’ needs. Your role is pivotal in demonstrating the value and capabilities of our products through compelling demos tailored to our account-based sales strategies. Working closely with our account executives, you will provide essential technical support, ensuring our solutions perfectly align with our clients' objectives and challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Write and design technical documentation and presentations about our products and technology.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design and deliver customized product demos to showcase the unique value of our AI-driven search and ads optimization solutions to prospective clients.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with account executives to understand client requirements and technical constraints, ensuring our demos and presentations are targeted and effective.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide technical expertise and support during the sales process, answering technical questions, and offering solutions that meet client needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assist in the development of sales strategies and materials, leveraging your technical knowledge to enhance our sales propositions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Act as a liaison between the sales and product development teams, relaying customer feedback and insights that can inform product enhancements and innovation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stay abreast of industry trends, competitive landscape, and technological advancements, continuously enhancing your presentations and knowledge base.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or a related technical field.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent technical writer and communicator. A passion for language and the liberal arts is a big plus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Loves engaging with a wide variety of technical customers in an enterprise sales context.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong technical acumen, with the ability to understand and demonstrate complex technology solutions effectively to a non-technical audience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent presentation and communication skills, with a proven track record of creating and delivering engaging demos.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a fast-paced, collaborative environment, supporting account executives in a technical sales capacity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with AI, machine learning, search, and advertising technology is highly advantageous.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to quickly learn new products, technologies, and industries.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$120K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$120K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US / Remote (US)</location><title>Applied AI Research Scientist - Computational Imaging</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>65547</job_reference><company>DeepNight</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/ca14b18b7a8db11193f2d4440e4d1fd8f25912de.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/deepnight</company_website><company_description>Building The Next Generation of Night Vision Devices</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/65547</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About DeepNight&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;DeepNight is building night vision with AI software. We are pushing the state of the art of computational imaging to build a new generation of night vision goggles that see in the dark using AI. We conduct novel research in computational photography, novel efficient neural architectures, and model compression techniques to build extremely efficient AI on the edge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;Torch/PyTorch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;DeepNight is a seed-stage startup that leverages the latest advancements in AI to push the boundaries in computational imaging at the edge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a talented Applied AI Research Scientist specializing in computational imaging to join our team. You will be responsible for conducting innovative research and developing advanced algorithms at the intersection of artificial intelligence and imaging technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Conduct research to explore novel approaches in computational imaging, leveraging artificial intelligence and machine learning techniques.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implement and optimize algorithms for real-time or near-real-time applications, considering computational efficiency and hardware constraints.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Evaluate and validate algorithms using experimental data and real-world scenarios, ensuring robust performance and reliability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stay up-to-date with the latest advancements in AI, machine learning, and imaging technology, and integrate relevant techniques into research projects.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Publish research findings in peer-reviewed conferences and journals, and contribute to patent applications when applicable.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferred Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ph.D. or equivalent experience in Computer Science, Electrical Engineering, or related field, with a focus on artificial intelligence, machine learning, computer vision, or computational imaging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong research background with a track record of publications in top-tier conferences or journals in relevant fields.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;PyTorch experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of imaging principles, including optics, sensors, and image formation processes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;Technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We use PyTorch on 8x H100 GPUs. We deploy our night vision AI onto silicon on chips. Techniques like model compression, quantization aware training, knowledge distillation, are utilized. Efficient image processing algorithms are implemented in Halide and C++.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$150K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$300K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>Boston, MA</location><title>Machine Learning Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>63832</job_reference><company>Nextera Robotics</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/98038d3f6de4865c9f869822e2af32391f49256e.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/nextera-robotics</company_website><company_description>AI-native Robotics</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63832</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Nextera Robotics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nextera Robotics is an AI-native Robotics and Industrial Automation company founded at MIT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;Python, Machine Learning, Computer Vision&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nextera Robotics&lt;/strong&gt; is a fast-growing industrial robotics and AI company founded by MIT alumni. Nextera has an A-list client base including Dunkin Donuts, Tesla, Gilbane Building Co., and other Fortune 500 companies. Nextera graduated from Y-Combinator S20 and raised significant funding from top-tier investors to support it's mission of solving industrial automation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working at Nextera is a great opportunity for those who love to get things done. We are a fast-paced, highly technical organization. Our teams are kept small and agile to limit layers of unnecessary process. Autonomy is expected. Every engineer gets to see their work transition from ideas to high-value products. The work is challenging, but highly rewarding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a perfect job for you if you are a strong programmer with versatile software development track record and a passion for AI and robotics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What you will be doing:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Help build and maintain state-of-the-art machine learning models for use in robotics, construction, energy and telecommunications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with engineers and annotators to grow a bank of high-quality training data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Machine Learning Operations (MLOps)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maintain and build cloud architecture for ML pipelines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skills and Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advanced training in mathematics, statistics, physics, computer science, or another highly quantitative field&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proven academic or industry experience with machine vision, object detection, ViTs, or related technology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent Python skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Structured approach to problem solving, creativity, strong communication skills, leadership skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with MySQL&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nice to Have:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Back-end experience with popular frameworks, Django knowledge is an advantage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We will be very excited to learn more about you and welcome you to the Nextera Robotics team!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$130K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$180K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>ML Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>63740</job_reference><company>Instawork</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/1712f8a08b08bb04e192934a1098d1b5144c875b.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/instawork</company_website><company_description>A flexible work app that connects businesses with hourly workers.</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63740</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Instawork&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instawork is the on-demand staffing app for hospitality gigs. We quickly and reliably match businesses with nearby qualified workers. We’re excited to enable our Professionals, a new generation of the emerging, diverse workforce, to be a part of the growing gig economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’ve been fortunate to be funded by some of the greatest investors in Silicon Valley: Benchmark (Bill Gurley), Y Combinator, SV Angel, Crunchfund, Steve Chen (co-founder of YouTube), Mike Vernal (VP of Product at Facebook), among many more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;Python, Machine Learning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're seeking an exceptional Machine Learning Engineer to be a founding member of our cutting-edge team. As a pioneer in this dynamic field, you'll play a pivotal role in shaping the future of work for over 5 million shift workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a founding ML Engineer, you'll be responsible for developing and deploying state-of-the-art machine learning algorithms that power our marketplace. You will collaborate closely with Product, Engineering and Design to personalize our marketplace. Your work will have a direct impact on the lives of millions of workers, helping them find the perfect shift that matches their skills, preferences, and availability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What You'll Do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*Be part of a team to implement machine learning algorithms to solve complex problems in real-time scheduling and workforce optimization*Gather, clean, and prepare large datasets for machine learning modelsImplement models using AI frameworks/platforms including LangChain, OpenAI, Bard and more*Build and maintain machine learning pipelines that are robust, scalable, and efficient*Collaborate with cross-functional teams to integrate machine learning solutions into production systems*Monitor and evaluate the performance of machine learning models and make continuous improvements&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;Technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Django, React, React Native, AWS, Neo4J&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://engineering.instawork.com/"&gt;https://engineering.instawork.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$140K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Durham, NC, US</location><title>Computer Vision and Optimization Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>63298</job_reference><company>BotBuilt</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/6c0f70c9a27028dd4b634603cfcc5021fc68ccb3.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/botbuilt</company_website><company_description>We use robots to build houses.</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63298</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About BotBuilt&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;BotBuilt is creating flexible robotic systems to solve the housing crisis. Our cutting-edge software and cost-efficient hardware allow us to improve the world by providing beautiful construction, safer job sites, and sustainable building techniques. The $600 billion residential construction industry is facing a massive labor shortage. Our robotic systems leverage the latest in rapid prototyping, artificial intelligence, and computer vision. By taking on some of the hardest technical challenges on earth, BotBuilt is ready to help solve one of society’s biggest problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;Machine learning, Computer Vision&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What does BotBuilt do?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We build robots that build homes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We collaborate with traditional home builders to enhance their construction process through speed, safety, and precision. Having already delivered framing components for multiple houses, our innovative building method is driven by a versatile team made of experts in robotics, computer vision, optimization, mechanical design, pcb layout, and algorithm design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What you'll do at BotBuilt&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design, implement, and optimize CV models.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Setup MLOps pipeline for continuous improvement of CV models.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Meet with contractors and understand their needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop optimizations that apply to important aspects of the construction industry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Your qualifications&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;We seek a dedicated and innovative software engineer with 3-5 years of experience to expand our capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Python is crucial.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated skill in Computer Vision, and/or Optimization.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of C++ is advantageous.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience deploying Computer Vision models is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Operations Research is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your role will encompass both pure Computer Vision projects, and cross-functional projects that involve integration with hardware teams. You'll own an important part of the technology stack that enables the robots to build the homes of tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Company Perks&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitive compensation and equity options.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Comprehensive health, vision, and dental insurance for you and dependents.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inclusive 401(k) match.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Generous PTO flexibility.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daily catered lunches and an array of snacks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Access to our company gym.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The BotBuilt Team&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our team is a distinguished collective of experts, including alumni engineers from NASA, veterans of the U.S. Special Operations Forces, and doctorates in Robotics and Civil Engineering. Bound by a shared mission, we harness advanced technology to address the critical challenge of housing shortages. Our unique blend of experience and passion positions us at the forefront of innovation in this field, poised to make significant impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Where to Apply&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply on our Rippling board: &lt;a href="https://ats.rippling.com/botbuilt/jobs/87be6bdc-a2ba-4272-8040-e160ecb379da"&gt;https://ats.rippling.com/botbuilt/jobs/87be6bdc-a2ba-4272-8040-e160ecb379da&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;Technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're designing custom hardware and software for building houses with robotic arms. ROS, Python, and/or CAD experience preferred but not required.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$90K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$130K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>AI / ML Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>63264</job_reference><company>Sieve</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/b247c36fd7cd016d5bb505d32429cd07b9acfcbb.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/sieve</company_website><company_description>The cloud for video &amp; audio AI</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63264</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Sieve&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sieve is a new kind of specialized cloud built specifically around video / audio understanding and generation use cases. We have a set of production-ready APIs available out of the box, and tooling that makes it easy to combine various models together in your apps — and share them with your team as an intuitive AI playground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sieve’s product comes with a lot of &lt;a href="https://www.sievedata.com/explore"&gt;pre-built, production-ready apps&lt;/a&gt; available out of the box. You’ll explore ways to combine new models to solve popular use cases, and make them work at high quality bars and quick speeds. It’s a combination of implementing models, optimizing them, and having intuition for the right ways to combine them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some good qualities to have include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;An interest in keeping up to date with the models coming out everyday&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience optimizing models to run faster&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;No need for a PhD but experience having built cool projects with ML models&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Love being in &lt;code&gt;CUDA&lt;/code&gt; hell. Just kidding, but experience in dealing with NVIDIA drivers and CUDA.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check out this page to learn more about the company and what it's like to work with us!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sievedata.com/about/jobs"&gt;https://sievedata.com/about/jobs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;Technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;As an early engineer, you’ll get to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;work on low level containerization, networking, and distributed systems problems impacting thousands of GPU workloads at any given moment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;write and deploy code that touches users every single day&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;work with the latest generative models&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;make decisions on product experience and design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;interact directly with customers in calls, shared Slack channels, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;We primarily code in Go, Python, and Rust. Additionally, we heavily utilize Redis, Prometheus, Loki, Grafana, MongoDB, Pulumi, and Clickhouse. Our frontend is build with Next.js.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>Software Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>60385</job_reference><company>Meru</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/00edfb93127d4366b2f890aa7fb0274a122e45c2.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/meru</company_website><company_description>A Smarter In-Basket for Physicians.</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/60385</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Meru&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meru is based out of San Francisco, CA, in the South Park neighborhood. We are building the next generation information acquisition system. We’re passionate about computers and language. We’re well-funded, post-revenue, and work with exciting late-stage startups and Fortune 500 companies. We’re hiring smart people profusely to grow our small team. Our benefits include top-tier health insurance, a generous 401(k) plan with matching, company-sponsored equipment, and stipends for employee education.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Come join Meru, and help us shape the future of knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;Torch/PyTorch, Python, Deep Learning, Reinforcement learning (RL), Amazon Web Services (AWS)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a founding role. You will work directly with Venkat (the CTO) to build deployment configurations and platform features for our customers. You will be expected to help with engineering across the stack, including model architecture research, latency optimization at both the software and hardware level, cloud infrastructure, and product roadmap. You will also work closely with our customers on onboarding, support, and keeping them happy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're looking for people who have demonstrable experience in deep learning research, cloud computing, software / hardware co-design. You are also expected to have strong organizational skills and strong problem solving skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Bachelor's degree in computer science / engineering and experience in engineering ML products is required. Graduate level work in deep learning and transformer models is strongly preferred. If you have experience building a strong engineering culture at an early-stage startup, we'd love to talk with you!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$100K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$140K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>Machine Learning Architect</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>61901</job_reference><company>Meru</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/00edfb93127d4366b2f890aa7fb0274a122e45c2.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/meru</company_website><company_description>A Smarter In-Basket for Physicians.</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/61901</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Meru&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meru is based out of San Francisco, CA, in the South Park neighborhood. We are building the next generation information acquisition system. We’re passionate about computers and language. We’re well-funded, post-revenue, and work with exciting late-stage startups and Fortune 500 companies. We’re hiring smart people profusely to grow our small team. Our benefits include top-tier health insurance, a generous 401(k) plan with matching, company-sponsored equipment, and stipends for employee education.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Come join Meru, and help us shape the future of knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;Torch/PyTorch, Python, Deep Learning, Reinforcement learning (RL), Amazon Web Services (AWS)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a founding role. You will work directly with Venkat (the CTO) to optimize our agent-based retrieval. You will be expected to help with engineering across the stack, including model architecture research, latency optimization at both the software and hardware level, cloud infrastructure, and product roadmap. You will also work closely with our customers on onboarding, support, and keeping them happy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're looking for people who have demonstrable experience in deep learning research, cloud computing, software / hardware co-design. You are also expected to have strong organizational skills and strong problem solving skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Master's degree in computer science / engineering and experience in engineering ML products is required. Graduate level work in deep learning and transformer models is strongly preferred. If you have experience building a strong engineering culture at an early-stage startup, we'd love to talk with you!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$100K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$140K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Chiyoda City, Tokyo, JP / San Francisco, CA, US / Remote</location><title>AI Researcher (Anime)</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>60810</job_reference><company>Spellbrush</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/fb441dcc9519c0cc22e2464b6b1c3b1ca462403b.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/spellbrush</company_website><company_description>Magic Anime Pictures</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/60810</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Spellbrush&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here at Spellbrush, we're passionate about making a good anime game. We also happen to be the world's leading generative AI studio — we're the team behind &lt;a href="https://nijijourney.com/"&gt;niji・journey&lt;/a&gt;.We are currently investigating how AI can be used to help human artists perform masterpieces in the most complex medium of our times: videogames.Our games are characterized by a no-compromise approach to well-balanced gameplay married to a truthful love of visual arts.If you love turn-based tactics games, please consider applying!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;Machine learning, Python, Torch/PyTorch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://app.ashbyhq.com/api/images/user-content/89c1442c-bd9c-46be-a910-20b49b5d9ffc/f100c26c-e91c-4f45-8750-f1b13a7714d3/cixelyn_scientist_doing_research_in_a_lab_coat_c7d3ec72-49af-465e-83d2-5ed3fab162ca.png" alt=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;The Anime Researcher Role:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're looking for an experienced AI Researcher to join our team and help us push the boundaries of AI and anime. You'll design and develop large-scale diffusion models with a primary focus on images, and secondary focus on other modalities like 3d, text, video and audio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;You may be a good fit if:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h3&gt;You love anime and the anime aesthetic.&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This one of the only labs in the world where you can combine your expertise on anime and deep learning to work on state-of-the-art anime models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You understand diffusion, or can get up to speed quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're looking for experienced researchers who aren't afraid of jumping headfirst into experimenting and designing massive models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;You're proficient in Pytorch (and maybe JAX too)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have a very large Pytorch codebase, and an equally large JAX codebase for large-scale TPU training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;You enjoy a tight loop between research and production.&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We pride ourselves on getting models from the lab into production quickly. Our research team works closely with our internal studio to both develop game-ready models, and deploy regular quality updates to niji・journey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;You're comfortable working on small, fast-paced teams&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We currently have a team of four on AI. You'll be working closely alongside some of the best AI researchers in the world, on the literal best image model in the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We also believe in the unmatched speed of in-person teams, and prefer on-site collaboration in either our primary research office in Tokyo (downtown Akihabara), or San Francisco. Visa sponsorships are available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;IMPORTANT:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the anime focus of this position, it is &lt;em&gt;required&lt;/em&gt; to answer the question "Who is your favorite waifu or husbando" when submitting your application through Bookface. Applications that fail to include a response to this question in the application message will NOT be reviewed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://app.ashbyhq.com/api/images/user-content/89c1442c-bd9c-46be-a910-20b49b5d9ffc/00e42897-0f4f-48f4-acc7-3874a6c77596/cixelyn_datacenter_77291509-26ba-4952-8eca-a6dad8f6c236.png" alt=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;Technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Spellbrush, we're pushing the boundaries of generative networks through our &lt;strong&gt;state-of-the-art diffusion text-to-image research&lt;/strong&gt;. There's no shorted of interesting tech challenges here:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research&lt;/strong&gt;: We make heavy use of Pytorch and JAX, and train large-scale models using both TPUs and GPUs. Our researchers spend each day developing and testing novel state-of-the-art diffusion models.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engineering&lt;/strong&gt;: We make use of a lot of Elixir for real-time backend systems, Python for machine learning, and lots of simulation and game logic code written in C# via Unity. We also have tons of internal tools and apps written in Typescript, React, and RN.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Infrastructure&lt;/strong&gt;: We've done everything from building our own in-house GPU supercomputer, to scaling up massive inference clusters in our own datacenters, typically orchestrating via some unholy combination of SLURM, kubernetes, and NATS.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$75K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US / Remote</location><title>LLMs and general AI Researcher/Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>60361</job_reference><company>Rosebud AI</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/0669f9afff20bf775d9b001b89480415cdb33109.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/rosebud-ai</company_website><company_description>Make games at the speed of thought.</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/60361</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Rosebud AI&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;About Us&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://rosebud.ai/"&gt;Rosebud.ai&lt;/a&gt; is building the AI Roblox.  We use generative AI workflows to accelerate game development and creative. The next few years of AI are going to define the coming few decades of the world. Some wait a lifetime for a moment like this. For those who have an inner fire to make something great, join us. Let’s build.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;About Us&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more on vision and team. Check out this 3 min video: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JuxMHfzUff0&amp;amp;ab_channel=Lishali"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JuxMHfzUff0&amp;amp;ab_channel=Lishali&lt;/a&gt;.We're the team that built&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://tokkingheads.com/"&gt;Tokkingheads&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;(2 million IOS downloads, all organic) that allows any portrait/photo/face to be animated in seconds with no skill, and Synth (&lt;a href="https://www.synth.run/"&gt;https://www.synth.run&lt;/a&gt;), a simple mobile app that allows users to create images based on Stable Diffusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re a team of PhD researchers, creatives and engineers backed by&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies?batch=w2020"&gt;Y Combinator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;with our seed led by Vinod Khosla at&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.khoslaventures.com/"&gt;Khosla Ventures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;with participation from&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://balajis.com/"&gt;Balaji Srinivasan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;**&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Former CTO Coinbase and A16Z GP),&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ilyasut"&gt;Ilya Sutskever&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(cofounder/chief scientist Open AI),&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kevinlin3/"&gt;Kevin Lin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(cofounder COO Twitch), &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hollyhliu"&gt;Holly Liu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;C&lt;/em&gt;o-founder Kaba,&lt;/em&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kungao/"&gt;Kun Gao&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(cofounder, CEO Crunchyroll), &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ljxie"&gt;Linda Xie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Founder Scalar Capital,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jon_Snoddy"&gt;Jon Snoddy SVP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;@ Walt Disney Imagineering,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/jeffdean"&gt;Jeff Dean&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;SVP Google Research,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/adamdangelo"&gt;Adam D'Angelo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;CEO Quora, and&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/calilyliu"&gt;Lily Liu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;cofounder&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://earn.com/"&gt;http://earn.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;Python&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Application Process&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fill out this form so we can get in contact with you: &lt;a href="https://airtable.com/shrZj3eXVXaUnV1KB"&gt;https://airtable.com/shrZj3eXVXaUnV1KB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;h2&gt;About Us&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://rosebud.ai/"&gt;Rosebud.ai&lt;/a&gt; building generative AI workflows to accelerate game development and creative. We want to empower indie devs to build games at the speed of thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're the team that built&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://tokkingheads.com/"&gt;Tokkingheads&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;(2 million IOS downloads, all organic) that allows any portrait/photo/face to be animated in seconds with no skill.&amp;nbsp; And Synth (&lt;a href="https://www.synth.run/"&gt;https://www.synth.run&lt;/a&gt;), a simple mobile app that allows users to create images based on Stable Diffusion. We’re a team of PhD researchers, creatives and engineers backed by&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies?batch=w2020"&gt;Y Combinator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;with our seed led by Vinod Khosla at&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.khoslaventures.com/"&gt;Khosla Ventures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;with participation from&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/karpathy?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor"&gt;Andrej Karpathy,&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://balajis.com/"&gt;Balaji Srinivasan&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;**&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Former CTO Coinbase and A16Z GP),&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ilyasut"&gt;Ilya Sutskever&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(cofounder/chief scientist Open AI),&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kevinlin3/"&gt;Kevin Lin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(cofounder COO Twitch),&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hollyhliu"&gt;Holly Liu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;C&lt;/em&gt;o-founder Kaba,&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jon_Snoddy"&gt;Jon Snoddy SVP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;@ Walt Disney Imagineering,&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/jeffdean"&gt;Jeff Dean&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;SVP Google Research and&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/adamdangelo"&gt;Adam D'Angelo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;CEO Quora.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why Join us?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;🚀 Join a Rocket Ship!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;🚀 Ship products that delight millions of users while having direct product impact on a small team (2 million downloads in over 180+ countries).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;🚀 Do cutting edge ML and full stack work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;🚀 Remote outside of SF Bay Area, or 4 day in person policy for Bay Area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;🚀 Work with a passionate, low ego, world class team!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our team is still quite small (&amp;lt;10), so you’ll have massive impact on the trajectory of the business from Day One.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;em&gt;Your Role&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ongoing research in generative assets creation methods in text domain&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Combining the full power of large language models with more traditional NLP algorithms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Investigating new methods for creating games&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implementing state-of-the-art generative methods from scratch, as well as modifying them, including LLMs for code generation and editing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prototyping ml models and pipelines to meet business requirements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Follow generative DL methods trends&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;You fit well if you have great experience in modern natural language processing dl based methods, if you can take some idea or business task, find good open source or implement simple methods to create prototype, package all of this for demo and always have ideas on how to iteratively improve (better quality, faster for inference, other workflows, …)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;em&gt;Requirements&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in generative DL in text domain&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Great experience in DL and traditional text processing methods&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in LLMs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Great pytorch knowledge&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dev tools - git, docker, clouds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in related domains (images processing, 3d graphics, video processing, gamedev) is a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;Technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;LLMs for code gen.Generative AI for 2D and 3D asset generationBrowser based games.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$50K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$180K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>Boston, MA, US</location><title>AI guided antibody design</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>59805</job_reference><company>Nabla Bio</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/55ab768ede08ceeb6e36143084cba599849464d0.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/nabla-bio</company_website><company_description>We use AI to design antibodies for intractable diseases</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/59805</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Nabla Bio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Antibodies need to possess a multitude of properties to be manufacturable, safe, and efficacious for patients. This is a hard engineering problem with a high a failure rate, because today’s discovery technologies rely on brute-force guess-and-check. At Nabla, we're building a protein design platform that enables us to build antibodies deliberately, with all the properties they need to reach and treat patients, and do so faster than we can today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learn more at: &lt;a href="https://www.nabla.bio/"&gt;https://www.nabla.bio/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;Biology, Torch/PyTorch, Python, Machine Learning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our mission is to enable pharmaceutical and biotech companies to bring more antibody therapies to patients. Using AI and massively parallel experimentation, we design antibodies that precisely bind the disease target at the right location, while minimizing manufacturability and toxicity risks. We are a well-funded, revenue-generating, bilingual company of wet- and dry-lab scientists, and are founded by AI and protein design experts from Harvard University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fueled by partnerships and increasing demand for internal R&amp;amp;D,  we will be looking to you to apply and develop ML-guided antibody design technologies in tight collaboration and feedback with our wet-lab. This will include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Developing novel strategies and optimizing existing ones to predict antibody function from sequence and structure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Developing methods to predict and design antibody-antigen interactions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop sequence- and structure-informed representations that enable multi-property antibody engineering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In collaboration with our wet-lab, designing antibody structures and sequences for functional measurement in frequent design-build-test cycles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s or master’s degree, with a PhD or equivalent preferred.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leading of a multi-month machine learning research project that resulted in a publication, or tool that has been impactful for your previous employer, lab, or other users.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of statistics and machine learning fundamentals. Practical experience developing deep learning models from scratch, and tuning existing ones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Python and PyTorch and commonly used higher-level frameworks for model training and hyperparameter tuning.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fluency with Unix environments, AWS, and GitHub&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are problem-focused, and interested in working in a high-intensity, fast-paced environment often driven by deadlines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You value unblocking colleagues before yourself, and are excited to mentor/train junior colleagues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;Technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nabla.bio/platform"&gt;https://www.nabla.bio/platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;Interview Process&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mt-0 prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A typical interview process looks something like:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Meeting with Frances or Surge for 30 minutes as an initial screen and to make sure we're on the same page.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Meeting with Surge or Frances (whomever you didn't meet the first time) to further assess technical and behavioral skills, as well as answer any new questions you had.&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;After this step, we'll ask you to sign an NDA. We do this so that we can be open about what we're working on, and so that you have all the information you need to make a decision.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;An on-site interview in Boston with the whole team; runs from ~9AM - 5PM.&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;In the morning, we'll present to you for an hour about what we're working on.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Then you'll give a 30-40 minute job talk to the whole team (usually takes 1-1.5 hours with questions). We'll brief you in advance as to what it should contain.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lunch together with the team&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In the afternoon, 1:1s with relevant members of the team.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shortly after that, we’ll ask to speak to ~3 references, and we may schedule another 30-45 minute follow-up discussion. This isn't usually another interview, and is more to clarify expectations for the role and answer any other questions you have.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If we're mutually excited about working together, we'll extend an offer!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;We aim to keep our process efficient and not waste either of our time. The whole process can be done in 2-3 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$100K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$250K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Medellín, Antioquia, CO / Remote</location><title>Data Acquisition Specialist (Colombia location)</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>60716</job_reference><company>Veryfi, Inc.</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/b363a44bfe1278786c4092bd157ce82f208e1a21.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/veryfi-inc</company_website><company_description>APIs to Liberate Trapped Data in Unstructured Documents</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/60716</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Veryfi, Inc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veryfi empowers organizations to transform their unstructured data in the form of receipts, invoices, purchase orders, checks, W2s and other business documents into structured data at scale. Their suite of data transformation APIs can be leveraged for many use cases in financial services to deliver valuable business intelligence in seconds. Trusted by enterprises and technology companies alike, Veryfi’s AI-based platform is being leveraged by companies worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veryfi is backed by NewView Capital (NVC), Act One Ventures, TI PLatform, Y Combinator and Zillionize&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veryfi Raises $12 Million To Use AI To Tackle The Unstructured Data Entry Market&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/rebeccaszkutak/2021/04/26/veryfi-raises-12-million-to-use-ai-to-tackle-the-unstructured-data-entry-market/?sh=886fe19183f8"&gt;https://www.forbes.com/sites/rebeccaszkutak/2021/04/26/veryfi-raises-12-million-to-use-ai-to-tackle-the-unstructured-data-entry-market/?sh=886fe19183f8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Untapped Potential of Unstructured Data&lt;a href="https://nvc.vc/perspectives/veryfi-the-untapped-potential-of-unstructured-data/"&gt;https://nvc.vc/perspectives/veryfi-the-untapped-potential-of-unstructured-data/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Capterra Reviews&lt;a href="https://www.capterra.com/p/141684/Veryfi-Receipts-and-Expenses/reviews/"&gt;https://www.capterra.com/p/141684/Veryfi-Receipts-and-Expenses/reviews/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;COME AND SAY G'DAY!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;Python&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location: Hybrid/Remote Work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a full-time Data Acquisition specialist, who has the ability to correctly identify patterns as becoming a specialized, but essential skill when dealing with large amounts of data. Diverse fields from cyber threat to genomics rely on accurately identifying, acquiring, and, at times, correcting a very specific pattern among a sea of potential targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What You’ll be Doing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are a regular expression expert comfortable dealing with texts from all over the world.  You don’t necessarily have to be fluent in many languages, just be able to process/manipulate many different languages, formats and symbols with ease.  The ideal candidate should be able to create/modify the patterns into classes/categories/rules with experience in automating and parallelizing tasks.  You have a working knowledge of python is necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CS degree is not essential, but a degree/experience is necessary in sufficiently technical or related fields, e.g bioinformatics data preprocessing, quantitative linguistics, fields where data extraction from a large number of logs/dataset is involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bonus:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent command of python if the candidate aspires to take on the role of task automation.MongodbLinux command line environmentExposure to cloud environments (AWS, GCP)Understanding of distance functions and how they relate to error correctionRegex experience with right to left languages, e.g. Hebrew and Arabic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice(s)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Salary Range Disclaimer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The base salary range represents the low and high end of the Veryfi salary range for this position. Actual salaries will vary depending on factors including but not limited to location, experience, and performance. The range listed is just one component of Veryfi's total compensation package for employees. Other rewards may include an open Paid Time Off policy, and many region-specific benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equal Opportunities and Accommodations Statement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veryfi is deeply committed to building a workplace and global community where inclusion is not only valued, but prioritized. We’re proud to be an equal opportunity employer, seeking to create a welcoming and diverse environment. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, family status, marital status, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, neuro-diversity, disability, age, or veteran status, or any other non-merit based or legally protected grounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We value diverse experiences, including those who have had prior contact with the criminal legal system. We are committed to providing individuals with criminal records, including formerly incarcerated individuals, a fair chance at employment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Where legally permitted, Veryfi requires all individuals attending or working out of Veryfi offices or visiting Veryfi clients to be fully vaccinated against COVID-19. For positions that can only be performed at an Veryfi office, candidates must be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 and present acceptable proof of vaccination by the date of hire as a condition of employment. For positions that require some in-office work or in-person client meetings, exceptions to these in-office or in-person job requirements may be made at the discretion of the business through June 2022, at which point full vaccination will be required. Veryfi will consider requests for reasonable accommodation as required under applicable law. To qualify as being fully vaccinated against COVID-19 there should have been a two week period after receiving the second dose (or any government recommended booster shot) in a 2-dose COVID-19 vaccine series, or a two week period after receiving a single-dose (or any government recommended booster shot) in a single dose COVID-19 vaccine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;Technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;(a) Native Mobile apps: Swift, Objective-C &amp;amp; Kotlin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(b) Backend: Python 3, TensorFlow, APIs on Django, Hub/Web on Flask&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(c) IaaS: AWS with auto deploys to 4 geographies (read the deployment posts by Andrew here &lt;a href="https://medium.com/the-road-to-silicon-valley"&gt;https://medium.com/the-road-to-silicon-valley&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(d) Database: Amazon Aurora&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$24K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$36K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>Medellín, Antioquia, CO / Remote</location><title>Data Annotation Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>65595</job_reference><company>Veryfi, Inc.</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/b363a44bfe1278786c4092bd157ce82f208e1a21.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/veryfi-inc</company_website><company_description>APIs to Liberate Trapped Data in Unstructured Documents</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/65595</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Veryfi, Inc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veryfi empowers organizations to transform their unstructured data in the form of receipts, invoices, purchase orders, checks, W2s and other business documents into structured data at scale. Their suite of data transformation APIs can be leveraged for many use cases in financial services to deliver valuable business intelligence in seconds. Trusted by enterprises and technology companies alike, Veryfi’s AI-based platform is being leveraged by companies worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veryfi is backed by NewView Capital (NVC), Act One Ventures, TI PLatform, Y Combinator and Zillionize&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veryfi Raises $12 Million To Use AI To Tackle The Unstructured Data Entry Market&lt;a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/rebeccaszkutak/2021/04/26/veryfi-raises-12-million-to-use-ai-to-tackle-the-unstructured-data-entry-market/?sh=886fe19183f8"&gt;https://www.forbes.com/sites/rebeccaszkutak/2021/04/26/veryfi-raises-12-million-to-use-ai-to-tackle-the-unstructured-data-entry-market/?sh=886fe19183f8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Untapped Potential of Unstructured Data&lt;a href="https://nvc.vc/perspectives/veryfi-the-untapped-potential-of-unstructured-data/"&gt;https://nvc.vc/perspectives/veryfi-the-untapped-potential-of-unstructured-data/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Capterra Reviews&lt;a href="https://www.capterra.com/p/141684/Veryfi-Receipts-and-Expenses/reviews/"&gt;https://www.capterra.com/p/141684/Veryfi-Receipts-and-Expenses/reviews/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;COME AND SAY G'DAY!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;Machine Learning, Natural Language Processing, Data Warehousing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veryfi is a YC-funded Silicon Valley startup that uses AI to understand documents like receipts and invoices. As a Data Engineer at Veryfi, you'll contribute to the evolution of our training data infrastructure and the development of new features and projects. You'll gather, process, and analyze diverse datasets to generate high-quality training data for our machine-learning models. Furthermore, by delving deep into our system, you'll have the autonomy to identify challenges and opportunities, taking ownership of developing solutions to refine existing tools and algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gather, process, and analyze diverse datasets to generate training data that fuels the development of our ML projects.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expand and optimize the training data pipelines to improve the speed and accuracy of our processes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with a cross-functional team to define requirements and prioritize development efforts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Essential Skills:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Python programming for data handling and processing, with experience in utilizing data science tools such as Pandas, NumPy, SciPy, and others.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical thinking with a focus on delivering results.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Meticulous attention to detail, ensuring accuracy and precision in all data handling and processing tasks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Enthusiastic about learning and adapting to new technologies and methodologies, particularly in the realm of Machine Learning (ML).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Innovation mindset, adept at challenging existing processes and driving positive change.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with regex development, software engineering principles, and Linux command line tools.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Natural Language Processing (NLP) techniques and libraries, including the use of Large - - -- - Language Models (LLMs) and supervised learning for document data extraction.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Effective organizational abilities, capable of managing projects independently from inception to completion.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exceptional verbal and written communication skills, effectively communicating problems, proposed solutions, and results to stakeholders in a multicultural environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Bachelor's degree in computer science, engineering, or a related field. Postgraduate studies are a plus but not required.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keywords: NLP, Patterns Detection, Data Labeling, Software Development, Data Engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;Technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;(a) Native Mobile apps: Swift, Objective-C &amp;amp; Kotlin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(b) Backend: Python 3, TensorFlow, APIs on Django, Hub/Web on Flask&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(c) IaaS: AWS with auto deploys to 4 geographies (read the deployment posts by Andrew here &lt;a href="https://medium.com/the-road-to-silicon-valley"&gt;https://medium.com/the-road-to-silicon-valley&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(d) Database: Amazon Aurora&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$24K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$36K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA</location><title>Research Scientist or Research Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>48397</job_reference><company>Exa</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/52045f1870e5f9705f78339ab4b3f96126403b66.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/exa</company_website><company_description>Web search rebuilt for LLMs</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/48397</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Exa&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Search is our interface to information. A search engine with new capabilities -- creativity, memory, analogy -- will change what we know and how we think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're looking for research scientists and research engineers to join our team. We have a lot of compute per capita and have a good shot at defining a future technology. If that sounds up your alley, here's what we're looking for:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have graduate level ML experience (or are an exceptionally strong undergrad)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have an eye for fundamental, novel architectures that can scale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You're comfortable implementing your own ideas and creating large-scale datasets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;(Research engineer applicants only) You have a good understanding of performance optimization and distributed computing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still apply even if you think you don't fit all the criteria—exceptionally good researchers often don't follow conventional paths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$120K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$250K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA</location><title>Machine Learning Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at>2024-07-13</posted_at><job_reference>15934</job_reference><company>Tempo</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/8d7bb4096474a73857a04dd3a797223c11e906d3.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/tempo</company_website><company_description>Live home fitness training powered by computer vision.</company_description><category>AI/Machine Learning Engineer</category><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/15934</url><description>&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About Tempo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tempo is a Series B consumer fitness startup backed by Founders Fund and Khosla Ventures that uses computer vision to deliver an unparalleled fitness training experience to your home. Our unique hardware solution gives amazing trainers the ability to see their class participants in real time and deliver detailed advice that was previously only possible in person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;span&gt;C++, Python, Machine Learning, CUDA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;At SmartSpot, you'll be responsible for improving our pipeline for processing 3D data of human exercise and for deepening our engines for workout recommendations, difficulty scaling, and personalization. We're looking for a creative problem solver who has broad knowledge of a variety of fields within machine learning, and is interested in building real world solutions that impact our customers directly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;B.A./B.S. in Computer Science or related technical field or equivalent practical experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;3+ years programming experience in C++&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2+ years of work experience in Machine Learning or Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong mathematical background (3D geometry, linear algebra, numerical methods, algorithms)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience with Python&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the state of the art in supervised learning research&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Immediate availability&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="company-section my-10"&gt;&lt;span class="text-xl"&gt;Technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="prose max-w-none prose-p:mb-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tempo's software ranges from iOS and React consumer applications to Python distributed applications on AWS to embedded 3D data analysis and compression libraries written in C++/OpenCL.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're exploring new technologies to optimize our analysis of our extremely unique dataset of human motion - teaching computers to detect mistakes in customers' technique to help them perform at their best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plus, we're using data science to deliver the first comprehensive fitness training that's based on &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; science, not bro science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><min_compensation>$100K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>annually</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job></jobs></source>